A Guide to the Harry Flood Byrd, Sr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Political Correspondence and Papers, 1933-1965
  - B. 1937-1940
    - Correspondence, W - Z, 1937-1940 (Box Box 167)
      Separate folders for: Mrs. Russell Wagers; Mrs. F. A. Walke; Bradford H. Walker; John S. Wallace, II; Thomas Wallner; J. F. Walter; J. B. Wampler; T. E. Warriner; T. C. Watkins; Mrs. R. C. Watts; E. M. Wayland; A. C. Weaver; Kyle M. Weeks; George B. West; Nathaniel S. Wheat; L. M. Whitacre; E. White; Nell White; I. P. Whitehead; Mrs. I. P. Whitehead; G. F. Whitley; J. J. Wicker; J. J. Wicker, Jr.; H. T. Wickham; J. E. Williams; R. G. Williams; Martin B. Williams; H. Willis; L. L. Willis; C. H. Wilson; Ernest Woodruff; C. A. Woodrum; J. P. Woods; J. S. Wren; G. A. Wright; R. S. Wright, Jr.; W. A. Wright; J. F. Wysor; Young Democratic Clubs of Virginia; and J. H. Yost
  - C. 1941-1944
    - Correspondence, Al - Bi, 1941-1944 (Box Box 168)
      Separate folders for: Albemarle County Democratic Committee; Alfalfa Club; T. C. Andrews; H. Apperson; Appointments: State, State ABC Board, and Judgeships; J. E. Arbogast; R. Arnold; Tom Atkinson; Dr. F. W. Barger; A. D. Barksdale; R. T. Barton; J. Battle; W. S. Battle; J. V. Bauserman; H. L. Baxley; W. W. Beverley; Biographical material of Harry Flood Byrd; and Lloyd C. Bird
    - Correspondence, Bl - By, 1941-1944 (Box Box 169)
      Separate folders for: R. E. Blackwell; S. O. Bland; Cynthia Boatwright; C. W. Bondurant; Joseph L. Borda; J. H. Bradford; Ralph O. Brewster; J. F. Bright; R. K. Brock; S. W. Brooks; David Bruce; J. S. Bryan; M. Bustard; T. G. Burch; R. H. Burke; and Harry Flood Byrd for President
    - Correspondence, Harry Flood Byrd for President, 1941-1944 (Box Box 170)
    - Correspondence, Harry Flood Byrd for President, 1941-1944 (Box Box 171)
      Separate folders for: John U. Barr; Zach Lamar Cobb; K. A. Crowley; and E. B. Germany
    - Correspondence, Harry Flood Byrd for President, 1941-1944 (Box Box 172)
      Separate folders for: S. B. Campbell; W. S. Campfield; C. Cannon; Bishop James Cannon; A. B. Carney; C. S. Carter; J. W. Carter; S. L. Carter; Stuart B. Carter; H. Cary; W. C. Caudill; A. B. Chandler; H. B. Chermside; S. M. Chitwood; and Morell Clarke
    - Correspondence, Cl - Da, 1941-1944 (Box Box 173)
      Separate folders for: N. E. Clement; F. Wilmer Coffman; H. E. Cole; G. B. Collings; L. P. Collins; E. R. Combs; Edward R. Conner; B. R. Council; E. T. Crawford; G. Crews; Jake & John Crim; K. A. Crawley; J. A. Currier C. C. Curtis; P. V. Dalton; Ted Dalton; C. W. Darden, Sr.; and C. W. Darden, Jr.
    - Correspondence, Da - De, 1941-1944 (Box Box 174)
      Separate folders for: C. W. Darden, Jr.; Darden Appointments -Federal Judgeships and State; Ralph Daughton; L. N. Davis; P. P. Deans; George DeHardit; and J. S. DeJarnette
    - Correspondence, Dem - Fo, 1941-1944 (Box Box 175)
      Separate folders for: Democratic conYention (National); Collins Denny, Jr.; Dr. George H. Denny; Everett M. Dirksen; F. M. Dixon; E. G. Dodson; R. Dorsey; G. L. Doughty; L. M. Downs; P. H. Drewry; J. T. Duval; N. B. Early; John H. East; H. Edwards; James O. Eastland; John W. Eggleston; D. Lane Elder; Allen J. Ellender; W. E. Elmore; R. B. Ely; W. G. Epes; A. A. Farley; J. A. Farley; Fauquier County Democratic Committee; N. R. Featherstone; C. R. Fenwick; H. L. Ferguson; Mrs. S. L. Ferguson; William McL. Ferguson; J. B. Fishhurn; E. A. Fitzpatrick; M. Fleischer; A. Fletcher; J. H. Fletcher; James W. Fletcher; J. W. Flood; Edwin J. Flynn; J. B. Fogleman; and C. Forney
    - Correspondence, Fr - Ha, 1941-1944 (Box Box 176)
      Separate folders for: Thomas Frank; T. M. Frazier; D. S. Freeman; F. H. Fuller; O. M. Gardner; T. M. Gaith right; P. Gerry; H. Gilmer; H. C. Gilmer; T. B. Glascock; P. Glass; M. W. Gold; M. G. Goode; Bernard C. Goodwin; C. O. Goolrick; T. P. Gore; J. H. C. Grasty; Garland Gray; Marvin L. Gray; Theodore F. Green; Noble J. Gregory; A. G. Gresham; H. E. Griffin; B. T. Gunter, Jr.; H. C. Guy; J. H. Hall; Stilson H. Hall; W. C. Hall; Ellis F. Hargis; C. Harkrader; Harvey F. Harris; Hiter H. Harris; Winder R. Harris; B. P. Harrison; M. D. Hart; Carl Hatch; Albert W. Hawkes; A. Wayne Hawks; and J. B. Haywood
    - Correspondence, He - L, 1941-1944 (Box Box 177)
      Separate folders for: C. L. Herring; C. Hill; W. S. Hildreth; H. H. Holt, Jr.; Homer A. Holt; L. H. Hooker; Herbert Hoover; J. Rolfe Horsley; Walter Y. Hosier; T. L. Hunter; Eppa Hunton, IV; S. Hutcheson; J. C. Jett; A. S. Johnson; C. M. Jordon; E. C. Johnson; F. E. Kellam; W. C. King; H. G. Kump; Dabney S. Lancaster; E. H. Lane; Josh Lee; J. Leslie; John L. Lewis; J. Lillis; List of House & Senate members who have sons or daughters in the Service; A. G. Lively; M. M. Long; L. E. Lookabill; R. F. Loper; C. C. Louderback; and O. Lowe
    - Correspondence, Mc - O, 1941-1944 (Box Box 178)
      Separate folders for: Patrick McCarran; C. P. McCue; E. O. McCue, Jr.; H. R. McKay; Kenneth McKellar; J. Maynard Magruder; Francis Maloney; Clarence Martin; J. D. Martin; T. E. Martin; W. B. Mason; G. A. Massenburg; J. H. May; E. Meeks; Carroll Menefee; H. Miller; J. M. Miller, Jr.; W. M. Minter; J. D. Mitchell; W. S. Moffett; F. P. Moncure; R. C. L. Moncure; E. S. Montague; B. F. Moomaw; E. B. Moore; E. H. Moore; Frank Moore; Grace Moore; M. R. Morgan; C. H. Morrissett; Charles T. Moses; Preston Moses; S. W. Moulding, Sr.; L. Muse; L. U. Noland; R. O. Norris, Jr.; H. and E. W. Opie; Organization of Executive Department Chart; John H. Overton; and T. W. Ozlin
    - Correspondence, Pa - Ro, 1941-1944 (Box Box 179)
      Separate folders for: A. A. Page; W. N. Page; John Paul; G. C. Peery; Philip C. Pendleton; R. L. Pennington; R. H. Perry; Poll Taxes; Mrs. John G. Pollard; Political Leaders list; D. L. Porter; J. L. Pratt; W. L. Prieur, Jr.; Robert Ramspeck; V. C. Randall; E. W. Rawls; S. W. Rawls; C. C. Reed; P. L. Reed; W. T. Reed, Jr.; Report of the Subcommittee concerning Voting in Virginia; John Q. Rhodes; R. H. Ricardo; E. R. Richardson; J. Richman; W. C. Rives; R. G. Roberts; A. W. Robertson; F. W. Rogers; and W. O. Rogers
    - Correspondence, Ro - Sm, 1941-1944 (Box Box 180)
      Separate folders for: F. D. Roosevelt; Mrs. Eleanor Roosevelt; A. L. Roper; W. S. Roop; John H. Russell; R. A. Russell; W. L. Sams; Salvation Army; David E. Satterfield; P. Saunders; Senate Rules Committee re: Senate Restaurant & Arbuckle emblezzlement; W. B. Shafer, Jr.; C. M. Shannon; C. Bascom Slemp; S. L. Slover; Sidney F. Small; H. W. Smith; L. F. Smith; O. F. Smith; P. M. Smith; and W. B. Smith
    - Correspondence, Sn - T, 1941-1944 (Box Box 181)
      Separate folders for: W. S. Snow; L. Spillman; C. V. Spratley; T. B. Stanley; A. P. Staples; State general election -Letters of congratulations; State Laws & Legislation; A. E. S. Stephens; R. B. Stephenson; E. R. Stettinius; Richard C. Stokes; A. T. Stroud; H. C. Stuart; J. W. Stuart; W. Swank; G. F. Switzer; J. R. Switzer; Robert A. Taft; F. S. Tavenner; D. W. Thomas; H. C. Thompson; John G. Townsend; L. Triplett; W. M. Tuck; and Millard E. Tydings
    - Correspondence, U - We, 1941-1944 (Box Box 182)
      Separate folders for: U. S. Exports to British Empire; C. F. Unruh; R. C. Vaden; Ray Allen Van Clief; F. Van Nuys; Virginia State Poll Tax; Virginia -Welfare Cases; Voting Record of Harry Flood Byrd; Russell F. Wagers; Mrs. F. A. Walker; B. H. Walker; F. C. Walker; J. G. Wallace, II; J. F. Walter; J. B. Wampler; T. C. Watkins; R. C. Watts; A. Weaver; Russell Weaver; and Sinclair Weeks
    - Correspondence, Wh - Y, 1941-1944 (Box Box 183)
      Separate folders for: Kenneth S. Wherry; E. White; G. F. Whitley; Kennon C. Whittle; J. J. Wicker; J. J. Wicker, Jr.; H. T. Wickham; Ralph E. Wilkins; J. E. Williams; Lewis C. Williams; R. G. Williams; C. H. Wilson; Woodrow Wilson Foundation Brochure; J. D. Wine; C. A. Woodrum; J. P. Woods; J. S. Wrenn; G. A. Wright; R. S. Wright; W. A. Wright; J. F. Wysor; Young Democratic Clubs of Virginia; and J. H. Yost
  - D. 1945-1948
    - Correspondence, A - Bi, 1945-1948 (Box Box 184)
      Separate folders for: Watkins M. Abbitt; Alfalfa Club; J. L. Almond, Jr.; T. C. Andrews; H. B. Apperson; Appointments re: Federal Judgeships, State ABC Board; State Judge ships, U. S. Court of Appeals, and U. S. Tax Court; Arlington County Democratic Executive Committee; R. Arnold; Arti facts; T. Atkinson; A. D. Barksdale; S. B. Barham; John U. Barr; J. S. Battle; W. S. Battle; H. L. Baxley; M. J. Beverley; W. W. Beverley; Theodore G. Bilbo; and Lloyd C. Bird
    - Correspondence, Bl - Co, 1945-1948 (Box Box 185)
      Separate folders for: R. E. Blackwell; S. O. Bland; Cynthia A. Boatwright (Mrs. R. G.); Armistead L. Boothe; Joseph L. Borda; Frank W. Boykins; J. H. Bradford; R. K. Brock; J. S. Bryan; T. G. Burch; Clarence G. Burton; Frank P. Burton; R. L. Burke; M. Bus tard; Hugh Butler; R. Button; Campaign -3rd District; S. B. Campbell; W. S. Campfield; Vincent A. Carlin; A. B. Carney; C. S. Carter; S. L. Carter; Hunsdon Cary; W. C. Caudill; Maj. Gen. B. F. Cheatham; H. B. Chermside; B. C. Clark; Tom Clark; N. E. Clement; Zach Lamar Cobb; L. P. Collins; and E. R. Combs
    - Correspondence, Cr - F, 1945-1948 (Box Box 186)
      Separate folders for: G. Crews; Jacob & John Crim; J. A. Currier Ted Dalton; C. W. Darden, Jr.; L. N. Davis; Q. C. Davis; P. P. Deans; Democratic Executive Committee; Democratic State Central Committee; C. Denny, Jr.; G. H. Denny; Jesse W. Dillon; E. G. Dodson; P. H. Drewry; C. J. Duke, Jr.; J. T. DuVal; N. B. Early; H. Edwards; D. L. Elder; W. E. Elmore; R. B. Ely; A. A. Farley; R. Feather stone; C. R. Fenwick; H. Ferguson; J. B. Fishburn; E. A. Fitzpatrick; J. W. Flannagan; A. Fletcher; J. W. Fletcher; J.W. Flood; J. B. Fogleman; C. Forney; T.M. Frazier; D. S. Freeman; and T. B. Fulgate
    - Correspondence, G - Ha, 1945-1948 (Box Box 187)
      Separate folders for: Vaughan Gary; T. M. Gaithright; General Assembly Election; H. Gilmer; P. Glass; Robert Glass; R. E. Glover; C. B. Godwin; M. G. Goode; Bernard C. Goodwin; C. O. Goolrick; Goverment Reorganization; Governorship -Virginia; W. M. Gravatt; Garland Gray; M. L. Gray; John L. Greene; A. G. Gresham; H. E. Griffin; Gubernatorial Campaign of 1945; B. T. Gunter; H. C. Guy; J. H. Hall; S. H. Hall; W. C. Hall; Porter Hardy, Jr.; E. F. Hargis; H. H. Harris; A. S. Harrison; B. P. Harrison; A. W. Hawkes; and Carl Hayden
    - Correspondence, Hi - L, 1945-1948 (Box Box 188)
      Separate folders for: W. S. Hildreth; C. H. Hill; Signey Hillman -Biographical material; H. H. Holt; R. D. Holt; L. Hooker; W. Y. Hosier; T. L. Hunter; S. Hutcheson; Jefferson Day Dinner; J. C. Jett; A. S. Johnson; Joint Committee on Reduction of Nonessential Expenditures; Robert F. Jones; C. M. Jordon; F. E. Kellam; Sidney Kellam; Marshall King; W. C. King; H. G. Kump; D. S. Lancaster; E. H. Lane; Letters of congratula tions; Fulton Lewis, Jr.; J. M. Lillie; L. E. Lookabill; M. M. Long; C. C. Louderback; O. Lowe; Luncheons; and Lynchings in the South
    - Correspondence, M - P, 1945-1948 (Box Box 189)
      Separate folders for: W. D. Macon; C. P. McCue; E. O. McCue, Jr.; J. B. McDaniel; Kenneth McKellar; J. D. Martin; G. A. Massenburg; Edward Meeks; H. Miller; J. M. Miller, Jr.; H. F. Minter; J. Douglas Mitchell; W. S. Moffett; E. S. Montague; B. Moore; E. H. Moore; C. H. Morrisett; Wayne Morse; C. T. Moses; L. Muse; L. U. Noland; R. O. Norris, Jr.; E. W. Opie; A. A. Page; Lester S. Parsons; J. Paul; G. C. Peery; Political; Poll Taxes & White Primary; Mrs. John G. Pollard; J. L. Pratt; and W. L. Prieur, Jr.
    - Correspondence, Q - St, 1945-1948 (Box Box 190)
      Separate folders for: V. C. Randall; C. C. Reed; P. L. Reed; W. T. Reed, Jr.; Chapman Revercomb; R. H. Ricardo; Rufus Roberts; James Robertson; A. W. Robertson; F. W. Rogers; W. O. Rogers; F. D. Roosevelt; Roosevelt's Inaguration -1945; R. A. Russell; Senate Rules Committee re: Senate Restaurant & Arbuckle Embezzlement; Senatorial Campaign; S. L. Slover; S. F. Small; H. W. Smith; O. F. Smith; W. B. Smith; H. F. Snead; Special session, 1944; and T. B. Stanley
    - Correspondence, Sta - Tu, 1945-1948 (Box Box 191)
      Separate folders for: State Senate; Richard C. Stokes; Strikes in Virginia; A. T. Stroud; W. A. Stuart; Suffrage Laws; G. F. Switzer; F. S. Tavenner; Teacher's Salaries; D. W. Thomas; and W. M. Tuck
    - Correspondence, Ty - V, 1945-1948 (Box Box 192)
      Separate folders for: M. E. Tydings; C. F. Unruh; University of Virginia; R. C. Vaden; R. A. Van Clief; Virginia Budget; Virginia Constitution re: Voting; Virginia Election Laws; Virginia Legislation -General; Virginia State Legislation; Virginia State Poll Tax; Virginia Welfare Cases; and Voting Record by year on Neutrality, UN, Trade, and Veterans
    - Voting Lists, Ac - Lo, 1946 (Box Box 193)
    - Voting Lists, Lu - Yo, 1937, 1940, and 1946 (Box Box 194)
    - Correspondence, W, X, Y, & Z, 1945-1948 (Box Box 195)
      Separate folders for: Henry A. Wallace; J. F. Walter; E. M. Wayland; R. M. Weaver; S. Weeks; Burton K. Wheeler; E. White; J. J. Wicker, J. J. Wicker, Jr.; Ralph Wilkins; L. C. Williams; R. G. Williams; H. Willis; C. H. Wilson; J. D. Wine; C. A. Woodrum; J. S. Wren; G. A. Wright; R. S. Wright, Jr.; J. F. Wysor; and J. H. Yost
  - E. 1949-1952
    - Correspondence, A - Be, 1949-1952 (Box Box 196)
      Separate folders for: W. M. Abbitt; Alfalfa Club; J. L. Almond; American Legion; T. C. Andrews; R. Arnold; J. S. Battle; and M. J. Beverley
    - Correspondence, Bi - Co, 1949-1952 (Box Box 197)
      Separate folders for: D. Woodrow Bird; C. A. Boatwright; A. L. Boothe; G. L. Boothe; J. L. Borda; Nina L. Boyd; William M. Boyle; T. G. Burch; C. G. Burton; J. F. Byrnes; A. B. Carney; C. S. Carter; Cartoons; H. Cary; L. P. Collins; and E. R. Combs
    - Correspondence, Cr - D, 1949-1952 (Box Box 198)
      Separate folders for: G. Crews; H. R. Cullen; T. Dalton; C. W. Darden, Jr.; L. N. Davis; G. P. DeHardit; Democratic National Committee; Democratic National Convention; Democratic National Convention Memoir; C. Denny, Jr.; J. W. Dillon; Everett Dirksen; E. G. Dodson; L. M. Downs; and Charles J. Duke, Jr.
    - Correspondence, E - Ha, 1949-1952 (Box Box 199)
      Separate folders for: Cyrus S. Eaton; Dwight D. Eisenhower; D. L. Elder; W. E. Elmore; C. R. Fenwick; H. L. Ferguson; Mrs. S. L. Ferguson; W. M. Ferguson; Fiscal Situation; E. A. Fitzpatrick; J. W. Fletcher; C. Forney; J. W. Flood; T. B. Fulgate; J. V. Gary; H. G. Gilmer; C. O. Gulrick; W. M. Gravatt; G. Gray; J. L. Green; A. G. Gresham; H. E. Griffin; H. C. Guy; J. H. Hall; P. Hardy, Jr.; D. L. Harrell, Jr.; B. P. Harrison; H. H. Harris; M. D. Hart; and Robert Hazelwood
    - Correspondence, Hi - J, 1949-1952 (Box Box 200)
      Separate folders for: Highway Department; W. S. Hildreth; C. H. Hill; Spessard Holland; H. A. Holt; Dowell J. Howell; Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner; A. S. Johnson; and Joint Committee on Reduction of Non essential Federal Expenditures
    - Correspondence, K - Lu, 1949-1952 (Box Box 201)
      Separate folders for: S. S. Kellam; W. C. King; E. H. Lane; A. G. Lively; M. M. Long; C. C. Louderback; O. Lowe; Scott W. Lucas; and Luncheons
    - Correspondence, Lu - M, 1949-1952 (Box Box 202)
      Separate folders for: Luncheons; G. A. Massenburg; J. H. May; C. P. McCue; E. O. McCue, Jr.; Francis Pickens Miller; W. S. Moffett; B. F. Moomaw; and C. H. Morrissett
    - Correspondence, M - Q, 1949-1952 (Box Box 203)
      Separate folders for: J. P. Neff; L. U. Noland; R. O. Norris; E. A. Opie; A. A. Page; Pepper Campaign; Drew Pearson; Poll Tax & Voting Laws; Mrs. J. G. Pollard; J. L. Pratt; and W. L. Prieur, Jr.
    - Correspondence, R - Sc; 1952 Senatorial Campaign, First District, 1949-1952 (Box Box 204)
      Separate folders for: Religious affiliations of members of the Senate, 82nd Congress; J. Q. Rhodes; A. W. Robertson; J. Robertson; Edward J. Robeson, Jr.; A. Schewel; W. Harry Schwartzchild, Jr.; and Senatorial Campaign, First District
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, First and Second District (Box Box 205)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Second District (Box Box 206)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Third District (Box Box 207)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Third District (Box Box 208)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Third District (Box Box 209)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Fourth District (Box Box 210)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Fourth District (Box Box 211)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Fourth and Fifth District (Box Box 212)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Fifth District (Box Box 213)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Sixth District (Box Box 214)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Sixth District (Box Box 215)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Sixth and Seventh District (Box Box 216)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Seventh District (Box Box 217)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Seventh and Eighth District (Box Box 218)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Eighth District (Box Box 219)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Eighth District (Box Box 220)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Eighth and Ninth District (Box Box 221)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Ninth District (Box Box 222)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Ninth and Tenth District (Box Box 223)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Out of State, A - G (Box Box 224)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Out of State, H - Q (Box Box 225)
    - Correspondence, 1952 Senatorial Campaign, Out of State, R - Z (Box Box 226)
      Separate folder for: Campaign material; chiefly excerpts of speeches and statements
    - Correspondence, Si - T, 1949-1952 (Box Box 227)
      Separate folders for: Signatures of Southern Senators in support of substitute for SR15; George Smathers; H. W. Smith; A. E. S. Stephens; T. B. Stanley; John C. Stennis; G. F. Switzer; D. W. Thomas; and W. M. Tuck
    - Correspondence, U - Z, 1949-1952 (Box Box 228)
      Separate folders for: University of Virginia; C. F. Unruh; Voting Record of Harry Flood Byrd; T. C. Watkins; J. B. Wampler; E. M. Wayland; R. M. Weaver; E. White; Robert Whitehead; J. J. Wicker, Jr.; H. Willis; J. S. Wren; W. A. Wright; J. F. Wysor; Young Democrat Clubs of America; J. H. Yost; and R. M. Youell
  - F. 1953-1956
    - Correspondence, A - B, 1953-1956 (Box Box 229)
      Separate folders for: W. M. Abbitt; Alfalfa Club; J. L. Almond; T. C. Andrews; R. Arnold; Ann and J. P. Arthur; J. W. Bailey; Robert Baker; J. S. Battle; Samuel M. Bemiss; C. F. Beverley; M. J. Beverley; Lloyd C. Bird; Bill for single appropriation and item Veto -proposed by Harry Flood Byrd; C. A. Boatwright; A. L. Boothe; Clarence J. Brown; T. A. Burke; H. Butler; Byrd Tax Bill [1954]; and J. F. Byrnes
    - Correspondence, C - D, 1953-1956 (Box Box 230)
      Separate folders for: John G. Carter; Cartoons; A. B. Chandler; H. B. Chermside; E. R. Combs; B. R. Councill; Kent Courtney; Mrs. Grasty Crews; Albert S. Cross; H. R. Cullen: T. Dalton; C. W. Darden, Jr.; G. P. DeHardit; Democratic National Committee; Democratic State Central Committee; Collins Denny, Jr.; T. E. Dewey; D. Dillon; E. G. Dodson; Ralph Dorsey; Lew W. Douglas; L. M. Downs; and W. G. Dunnington
    - Correspondence, E - G, 1953-1956 (Box Box 231)
      Separate folders for: H. H. Edwards; A. J. Ellender; Mr. & Mrs. W. E. Elmore; Federal Housing Administration Investigation; C. R. Fenwick; H. Ferguson; E. A. Fitz patrick; Ralph E. Flanders; J. W. Fletcher; J. W. Flood; Flood Control; J. B. Fogleman; J. V. Gary; Gasoline Tax; General Assembly & Democratic Committee Assignments; General -Virginia affairs; Walter F. George; P. Gerry; Henry Gilmer; H. C. Gilmer; P. Glass, Jr.; Barry Goldwater; C. O. Goolrick; Goshen Pass; J. L. Green; T. F. Green; Marvin Griffin; George P. Grove; Gubernatorial campaign; and Harry Guggenheim
    - Correspondence, H, 1953-1956 (Box Box 232)
      Separate folders for: J. W. Hanes; P. Hardy, Jr.; Robert M. Harriss; A. S. Harrison; B. P. Harrison; Mrs. A. Paul Hartz; A. W. Hawkes; Thomas C. Hennings; Highways; W. S. Hildreth; K. V. Hoffman; and George Humphrey
    - Correspondence, I - Lo, 1953-1956 (Box Box 233)
      Separate folders for: Jackson-Jefferson Day Dinner; Pat Jennings; E. C. Johnson; Lyndon Johnson; Joint Committee on Reduction of Nonessential Federal Expenditures; F. E. Kellam; S. Kellam; John F. Kennedy; James Kilpatrick; E. H. Lane; Local Committeemen Addresses -Va.; and C. C. Louderback
    - Correspondence, Lu, 1953-1956 (Box Box 234)
      Separate folders for: Luncheons
    - Correspondence, Lu - L, 1953-1956 (Box Box 235)
    - Correspondence, M - Pre, 1953-1956 (Box Box 236)
      Separate folders for: G. A. Massenburg; G. Edmond Massie; John L. McClellan; George Meany; Robert R. Merhige. Jr.; B. F. Moomaw; E. B. Moore; C. H. Morrissett; True D. Morse; B. T. Newton; R. O. Norris, Jr.; A. A. Page; Poll Tax & Voting; Mrs. J. G. Pollard; J. L. Pratt; and Presidential Campaign re: T. C. Andrews and D. D. Eisenhower
    - Correspondence, Pre - R, 1953-1956 (Box Box 237)
      Separate folders for: Presidential Campaign re: Adlai Stevenson and General Correspondence; W. L. Prieur, Jr.; Sam Ryaburn; R. E. A.; W. T. Reed, Jr.; Remarks honoring Harry Flood Byrd on his 20th year in the Senate; A. W. Robertson; and Ernest Robertson
    - Correspondence, S - Tha, 1953-1956 (Box Box 238)
      Separate folders for: Leverett Saltonstall; D. E. Satterfield, III; Allen Shivers; H. W. Smith; Margaret Chase Smith; T. B. Stanley; A. E. S. Stephens; A. E. Stevenson; W. F. Stone; Lewis Strauss; H. C. Stuart; G. F. Switzer; Stuart Symington; Thank you notes, etc., A -R
    - Correspondence, Tha - V, 1953-1956 (Box Box 239)
      Separate folders for: Thank you notes, etc., S -Z; Mr. & Mrs. James M. Thomson; Samuel Thrasher; Travel; W. M. Tuck; Samuel Ungerleider; Mary Washington College; University of Virginia; Virginia Debt; Virginia Judgeships; and Votes cast for Governor, Lt. Governor and Attorney General
    - Correspondence, W - Z, 1953-1956 (Box Box 240)
      Separate folders for: S. Gardner Waller; C. W. Wampler; E. White; J. L. Whitehead; Conrad Wirth; J. S. Wren; and J. F. Wysor
  - G. 1957-1960
    - Correspondence, Ab - Al, 1957-1960 (Box Box 241)
      Separate folders for: W. M. Abbitt; Sherman Adams; Holmes Alexander; Alfalfa Club; and J. L. Almond re: Federal Judgeships and Gubernatorial Campaign, A -S
    - Correspondence, Al - B, 1957-1960 (Box Box 242)
      Separate folders for: J. L. Almond re: Gubernatorial Campaign, T -Z, and Integration; T. C. Andrews; Anti Massive Resistance; R. N. Arnold; T. Atkinson; Robert G. Baker; Ross Barnett; John S. Battle; W. C. Battle; S. M. Bemiss; Ezra Taft Benson; M. J. Beverley; Lloyd C. Bird; C. A. Boatwright; A. 1. Boothe; F. Boykin; Paul Butler; D. Tennant Bryan; and J. F. Byrnes
    - Correspondence, C - D, 1957-1960 (Box Box 243)
      Separate folders for: David Carliner; Mrs. A. B. Carney; C. S. Carter; Lenoir Chambers; A. B. Chandler; Cartoons; H. B. Chermside; B. R. Councill; G. Crews; Carl T. Curtis; Virginius Dabney; T. Dalton; Price Daniel; C. W. Darden, Jr.; L. N. Davis; G. P. DeHardit; E. DeJarnette; Democratic Convention; Democratic District Committees; Democratic National Committee; Democratic State Central Committee; C. D. Dillon; J. W. Dillon; E. G. Dodson; R. N. Dorsey; Thomas N. Downing; Allen Drury; W. F. Duckworth; and W. Dunnington
    - Correspondence, E - Hu, 1957-1960 (Box Box 244)